ILGWU. David Melman papers, 5780/152
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ILGWU Convention: Delegates, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Delegate appropriation entitlements per local based on 1970 census, comparison with 1968; delegate and guest count at convention
- ILGWU Convention: Financial Reports, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Printed "Financial and Statistical Report, January 1, 1968 to December 31, 1970, submitted by Louis Stulberg, President, General Secretary-Treasurer, Thirty-Fourth Convention, May 6, 1971"; general office balance sheets; convention worksheets; schedule of donations to organizations; staff illness fund, special assistance fund, staff retirement fund, death benefit fund, and label promotion fund balance sheets
- ILGWU Convention: Financial Report, President, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Photocopy of printed financial report, with hand notations; four pages of notes for President Stulberg's financial report to the convention
- ILGWU Convention: Signage, Banquet, Seating, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Photocopies of photographs of signage at convention hall (originals held in Kheel photo archives); list of locals and delegate counts for each; seating charts showing delegations and number of delegates; invoice from Craftsmen Photo Company for convention floor plans; printed banquet ticket
- ILGWU Convention: Staff, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Lists of staff at convention, bonus/expense reimbursements
- ILGWU Convention: Convention Call, Planning, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Convention Call announcing convention to locals; outline of procedure for election of delegates and local officials; return forms for elections; memo to all affiliates requesting resolutions; memo requesting banners; memo re per diem allowances for delegates; registration instructions; blank souvenir convention memo pad; printed program, 33rd Convention, listing speakers, agenda; hand-lettered 4 ¼ by 7 inch sign, "Official Car International Ladies Garment Workers Union," with union label of the Sign and Pictorial Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America
- ILGWU Convention: Census, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Printed report, "Census Report 1967"; memo to locals with questionnaire re number of members employed in various trades; lists of new locals, locals out of existence, and locals merged, 1/1/65 – 12/31/67
- ILGWU Convention: Delegate Seating, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  List of locals and delegate counts for each; seating charts showing delegations and number of delegates
- ILGWU Convention: Financial Report, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Printed "Financial and Statistical Report, January 1, 1965 to December 31, 1967, submitted by Louis Stulberg, President, General Secretary-Treasurer, Thirty-Third Convention, May 23, 1968"; printed "Financial Report, General Funds, 1967, compiled by the Auditing Department"; printed "Employer Contributed Welfare Funds; printed Report of the Health & Welfare Retirement and Supplementary Unemployment Funds, 1967"; printed "Labor Organization Annual Report Form LM-2 and Instructions, U.S. Department of Labor"; printed "Instructions for Labor Organization Annual Report, LM-3"; letters from Union Welfare Bureau and Union Auditors soliciting business; typed draft of financial report narrative with handwritten editing notation; typed and handwritten balance sheets, membership census, dues income per local
- ILGWU Convention: Financial Report, Proofs, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Several stages of production proofs of printed report
- ILGWU Convention: Balance Sheet, General Office, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  General Office balance sheets, label promotion fund, special assistance fund, donations to organizations
- ILGWU Convention: Balance Sheets, Death Benefit Fund, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  Printed "Report 1965-1967 DEATH BENEFIT FUND, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 33rd Convention, ILGWU, May 1968, Atlantic City, NJ"; balance sheets
- ILGWU Convention: Staff Retirement Fund, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  Printed "1967 Report of the Health and Welfare Retirement and Supplementary Unemployment Funds, January 1, 1967 – December 31, 1967"
- ILGWU Convention: Census, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  Balance sheets showing net changes in membership by local, by geographic region, and total aggregate,1/1/62-1/1/65; dues revenue, 1903-1964
- ILGWU Convention: Delegate Seating, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  Three seating charts showing delegations and number of delegates for each
- ILGWU Convention: Financial Reports, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  Printed "Financial and Statistical Report, January 1, 1962 to December 31, 1964, submitted by Louis Stulberg, General Secretary-Treasurer, Thirty-Second Convention, Deauville Hotel, Miami Beach, Fla., May 12, 1965"; typed draft stages, associated balance sheets
- ILGWU Convention: Financial Reports, Proofs, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- ILGWU Convention: Financial Reports, Balance Sheets, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  Donations to organizations, label promotion fund, staff retirement fund, death benefit fund
- ILGWU Convention: Financial Reports, Balance Sheets, Assets, Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Labor Day Parade; March on Washington; Advance for National Severance Fund; check accounts, listing banks
- ILGWU Convention: Financial Reports, Balance Sheets, Convention Worksheets, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- ILGWU Convention, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  May 23-June 1, 1962, Convention Auditorium, Atlantic City, NJ. Printed "Financial and Statistical Report, January 1, 1959 to December 31, 1962, submitted by Louis Stulberg, General Secretary-Treasurer, Thirty-First Convention, Atlantic City, NJ, May 23-June 1, 1962"; memo to locals requesting flowers; memo to staff re expense reimbursement, list of staff by name, with reimbursement amounts; list of 1962 staff not at 1959 convention
- Mergers: New York City Health and Welfare Funds, Committee, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Edited report, "Toward a National Health And Welfare Fund: A Policy Statement And Program Outline"; committee meeting agenda and minutes; minutes of first Sportswear Joint Board Delegates' Meeting; handwritten notes; letter from attorney outlining merger steps for national health and welfare plan; resolutions
- Mergers: New York City Health and Welfare Fund, Resolutions, 1977-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Resolutions approving merger of New York City locals into the Sportswear and Allied Workers' Joint Board. Mergers include New York Coat, Suit, Dress, Rainwear and Allied Workers' Union, locals 10, 22, 23-25, 1- 35, 40, 66, 80-48, 91 (Children's Dress – Infants Wear, Housedress and Bathrobe Makers Union), 105, 155 (Knitgood Workers)
- Mergers: Pennsylvania, Hazelton Opposition, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Petition signed by members of Local 225, Hazelton, opposing closing and merger with office in Pittston; letters opposing closing: from Greater Wilkes-Barre Labor Council district manager to Pres. Mazur, opposing mergers as politically harmful to the labor movement, July 24, 1987; from member of Local 225 to Pres. Mazur, April 29, 1987; from president of Alliance to Revitalize Center-City Hazelton, Inc., to vice president Sol Hoffman, April 29, 1989; from president of United Labor Council of Lower Luzerne and Carbon Counties, April 30, 1987; from Local 14, Office & Professional Employees, AFL-CIO, April 30, 1987; from Local 1648, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, May 1, 1987; from member in Hazelton, April 30, 1987, with reply from Hoffman explaining rationale for merger, May 12, 1987; question & answer sheet outlining rationale for closing Hazelton; letter from Hazelton district manager to Sol Hoffman listing manufacturing shops in Schuylkill County, April 27, 1987; list of Hazelton District Council officers and members; resolutions approving merger; newspaper clippings
- Mergers: Pennsylvania, Harrisburg-Reading, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Resolutions approving merger: Central and Western Penna. and Reading District Council (Reading-Pottstown Local 93 and Trenton-Wilmington District Local 217-228); memo re wildcat strike at Aster Knitting Mills, local 93, Reading, June 10, 1987
- Mergers: Pennsylvania, Scranton-Shamokin, 1985-1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Resolutions approving mergers: original signed for the Scranton District Council, locals 109, 131, and 365, 8/23/89; for the Scranton-Shamokin-Sunbury-Pottsville District Council; financial statement for Shamokin-Sunbury-Pottsville District Council, locals 185-306-351, with hand notation "Resolution for merger passed Aug. 9, 1989"; meeting minutes
- Mazur Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Media Training, 1973-1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Media training kit by Michael Sheehan Associates, affiliated with Ogilvy Mather Public Affairs; script re evils of homework; handwritten notes, newspaper clippings, late 1980s?
- New York City: Fire Museum, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Correspondence with FDNY and Fire Museum re Triangle Shirtwaist Fire video; publicity material re Fire Museum, May-June 1987
- Imports Task Force [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Transcript of testimony before the Trade Policy Staff Committee: "The Economic Effects of a North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) on the U.S. Apparel Industry," Aug. 29, 1991; congressional roll call voting record on Textile and Apparel Act of 1987, with cover memo to ILG regional directors; copy of new version of bill, memo analyzing different versions; lobbying/public relations strategy handbook, "FFACT Battle Plan, 1998 Confidential"; call to action to retirees; memo re lobbying non-sponsors of bill who are up for re-election; copy of "dear colleague" letter by Senate sponsors, list of recipients; list of number of all employees in the apparel and knit mills by state, 1973-1987; newspaper clippings
- Imports Task Force [folder 2 of 2], 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  "Statement of Jay Mazur, President, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Before the Subcommittee on Trade, Committee on Ways and Means, U.S. House of Representative, May 18, 1987," and before the Committee on Finance, U.S. Senate, July 30, 1987, in support of the Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987; Minutes of the Task Force on Imports, 6/16, 6/23, 7/7, 7/21/, 7/24/87; list of ILG locals by state and congressional district, identifying congressional representatives; list of Senate and House cosponsors of the bill by state; newsletter, "ILGWU Memo/For Staff Only, Special Override Issue" May 1986; leaflets, newspaper clippings
- Vacation and Holiday Task Force, 1986-1989 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Survey form, "Vacations Paid Through Union Funds"; newsletter, "Local 23-25 News," Feb. 1989, with headline: "Major Changes Coming in Holiday Pay"; news bulletins, From China Town Press, from Centre Daily News, 1/88-1/89; correspondence with data processing firm, spreadsheets, analysis of cost effects under different policy scenarios, 1987; "Summary of Additional Cost For Proposed Vacation Benefit Rules Change," 9/7/88
- Vacation and Holiday Task Force: Financial Data, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  Several drafts, interim reports, and final reports of committee and subcommittees, 1987-88; minutes and recommendations of preliminary committee meetings, 1985; proposals; handwritten notes
- Vacation and Holiday Task Force: Reports, 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  Financial statements of health and welfare funds of various regions; spreadsheets comparing benefits from region to region; financial and statistical report of the Staff Retirement Fund, 1/1/86-11/30/86
- Vacation Surveys [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Printed "Northeast Department ILGWU Health & Welfare Fund," September 1985; printed "Summary of Benefits, Eastern Region, ILGWU Health and Welfare Benefit Program, July 1984 (English and Spanish); completed questionnaires, Northeast Dept., New England, New York State Eastern Region, Pacific Northwest District Council, Eastern Pennsylvania Region, Philadelphia-South Jersey District Council, New Jersey Region, Central States Region, Puerto Rico, with printed descriptive summary of plan, in Spanish; list of manufacturing associations under agreement, eligibility rules, Northeast Dept.; "Basic Plan, Northeast Department ILGWU Health and Welfare Fund (as amended August 20, 1985)"
- Vacation Surveys [folder 2 of 2], 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Spanish. Printed "For Your Health and Welfare…Know Your Benefits, Local 91-105 ILGWU" (English and Spanish); completed questionnaires of local 62-32 (Intimate Apparel Workers' Union), local 91-105 (Children's Wear and Allied Workers' Union), local 10, local 66-40, New York Coat, Suit, Dress, Rainwear & Allied Workers' Union (full bylaws attached), local 132-98 (Plastic, Metal Novelty and Allied Workers' Union), local 23-25 (New York Joint Board Health and Welfare Fund)
- Vacation Surveys: Southeast and Upper South, Surveys and Agreements, 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  Printed "Health and Welfare Benefits: Summary Plan Description, Southeast Region"; response to questionnaire, noting differences, with attachments, Upper South Department, 9/16/87; bylaws of the Southeast Region (as amended November 1984); agreements with Cameo Curtains, division of CHF Industries (Memphis, TN) and local 641, 4/1/85; Joy Fashions, Columbus, GA, and local 117 4/3//86; Sandra Sportswear, Weaver, AL, and local 363, 1/1/87; T.H.M. Manufacturing, Inc., and local 302, 1/1/85; Dary Sue Fashions, Inc., Piedmont, SC, and local 124, 12/14/82; Cape Coral Togs, Cape Coral, FL, and local 305, 1/1/87; Prattville (division of Smoler Bros., Inc.), Montgomery, AL, and local 310, 9/1/82; handwritten notes
- Vacation Funds: California, 1983-1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Printed "Agreement, Pacific Northwest District Council, ILGWU, and Locals No. 101, 213 and 214"; "Rules and Regulations of the ILGWU – Employers Vacation, Health and Welfare Fund (as amended, September 1983)"; "ILGWU – Blue Cross of California Health Insurance Plan Description," benefit change effective August 1, 1986; lists of eligibility requirements for vacation pay, 1978 and 1986; handwritten notes
- Vacation Member Complaints, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  Handwritten letters from members, appeal forms, notes
- Williamsburg Organizing: Campaign Outreach, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  Press releases from NYS Department of Labor re labor law violations, esp. homework, 1987-90; lists of members, Citizens' Committee for Justice in Brooklyn; letters urging support, with list of recipients (labor leaders, clergy, elected officials, community leaders), 1/90; press release from ILG Western States Region re legislation introduced by California assemblyman Tom Hayden holding garment retailers jointly liable with manufacturers for labor law violations, 3/2/90; letter from ILG president Mazur to Brooklyn District Attorney Charles Hynes re criminal case against Three Sisters Sportswear, 1/24/90; letter from Mazur to Daily News praising coverage of working conditions, 1/24/90; letter to congressman Stephen Solarz's office from ILG (Melman), 1/19/90; letter from ACTWU president Jack Sheinkman to members of Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union in support of campaign, with note from Sheinkman to Mazur that 2,000 letters had been sent; letter from Sonny Hall, president of Transport Workers' Union, to members in support; ILG memo re possibilities for church-union partnership, list of clergy; draft letter by New York City Labor Religion Coalition to ILG vice president Susan Cowell
- Williamsburg Organizing: Campaign Outreach, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  Spanish. List of campaign members, 12/30/89; fact sheet sent to members, Campaign for Justice in Brooklyn, 12/29/89; "Statement of Support by the Catholic Religious Community of Brooklyn for the Workers Employed by the Williamsburg Trade Association Who Are Striving to Organize a Real Union" with cover letter from ILG vice president Susan Cowell to Msgr. Basler asking for support, 12/29/89; letter from Cowell to Jewish Labor Committee; letter to NLRB from ILG legal department seeking immediate injunction against Williamsburg Trade Association, 12/12/89; correspondence between congressman Stephen Solarz and ILG vice president Evelyn Dubrow, 12/89; letters to Black Trade Unionist Leadership Committee, Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, and Longshoremen's Assoc. from ILG vice president Edgar Romney, 12/89; letters from Mazur and Romney to Brooklyn District Attorney Elizabeth Holtzman, City Council president Andrew Stein, state senators, NYS AFL-CIO, clergy, community leaders; other letters urging support, with list of recipients, 11/20/89; letter from Dennis Rivera, president, Local 1199, Drug, Hospital, & Health Care Employees Union, to Mazur and Romney, expressing support, 11/89; list of prominent Hispanics to contact, 10/89; "Testimony of Rev. Fred Davie, Jr., Before the Department of Labor Hearings on Industrial Homework in the Women's Apparel Industry, New York, March 30, 1989"; "Afternoon Session" (Archdeacon Michael S. Kendall, Episcopal Diocese of New York, before Judge Vittone); meeting agenda "on local 17-18 campaign," 1/2/89, with list of employer members of the Williamsburg Trade Association, showing size of workforce at each; letter from Jewish Community Relations Council to Washington Post, objecting to news coverage (clipping attached), 12/1/86; edited draft of proposed leaflet in Spanish and English; leaflet; handwritten notes
- Williamsburg Organizing: Domsey, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  Fact sheets, Campaign for Justice in Brooklyn; newspaper clippings, Daily News, New York Post, Newsday, New York Times, Women's Wear Daily, Amsterdam News, The Tablet, Craine's New York Business; correspondence with National Council of Young Israel; notes from meeting with rabbi, Young Israel Congregation; letter from Mazur to congressman Major Owens requesting intervention with NLRB to expedite election; letter from Rep. Owens to Department of Labor requesting investigation of labor law violations by Domsey Trading Company; letter to judge from Domsey attorney requesting injunction to further limit number of picketers due to anti-Semitic remarks by picketers; letter from ILG attorney re racist provocations by Domsey management; letter to NYC Human Rights Commission by Jewish community activist attesting to Domsey management remarks to picketers; correspondence between congressman Stephan Solarsz, ILG, and Domsey management; affidavit by strikers re harassment on picket line; WTA ad in Greenline, North Brooklyn Community News; letter from Mazur to NYPD commissioner re firebombing of home of Domsey employee, summons to Domsey manager to appear before criminal court for harassment, order of protection by employee against Domsey manager, deposition by Domsey employee re harassment; article reprints, "Economic Affairs," from Justice and Judaism, Albert Vosspan and Rabbi Eugene Lipman, 1959, and "Labor – Rights and Responsibilities." from Issues of Conscience: The Way of the Upright, A Jewish View of Economic Justice, by Rabbi Richard Hirsch, 1973
- Williamsburg Organizing: Williamsburg Trade Association, 17-18 List, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  Spanish. Lists of employers/garment shops belonging to the Williamsburg Trade association and its "sweetheart" union, 17-18, memo inquiring whether any received work from union jobbers, invoices and spreadsheets supplying that information; lists of WTA board members; notes re Three Sisters (aka Southland Knitwear and Metropolitan Knitwear); company profiles for J.A. Knitwear, subsidiary of Spectex Industries, Inc (10/10/89), Techknits, Inc. (7/14/89), Mademoiselle, Inc. (6/14/89); financial report on Mademoiselle re new plant construction debt, 7/26/90, related newspaper clipping; Dun & Bradstreet financial report on Damas Atlantic Ltd (Inc.), 12/31/89; list, Government Assistance to Williamsburg Trade Assoc. Firms; newsletter from NYC Office of Business Development (OBD News) re grants; photocopies from directory of grants; excerpted copy of Leslie Fay master agreement re jobbers
- Maidenform, Bayonne and Perth Amboy [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Maidenform, Bayonne and Perth Amboy [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Maidenform Florida Cutting Plant, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Maidenform Florida Distribution, 1982-19902 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Maidenform: West Virginia Agreement, 1969-1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Maidenform: Edison New Jersey Contracts, 1975-1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Maidenform Master Agreement: Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Maidenform Master Agreement: Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Maidenform, Incorporated: Letter Agreement, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Maidenform: Letter Agreement, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Maidenform: Negotiations, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Maidenform: Negotiations, 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Maidenform: Renewal Notices, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Maidenform, Incorporated: Negotiations, 1975-1982 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Maidenform: General File [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1985 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Maidenform: General File [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1985 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Maidenform: New Jersey Correspondence [Folder 1 of 2], 1979-1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maidenform: New Jersey Correspondence [Folder 2 of 2], 1979-1986 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Maidenform: New Jersey Correspondence [folder 1 of 3], 1987 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Maidenform: New Jersey Correspondence [folder 2 of 3], 1987 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Maidenform: New Jersey Correspondence [folder 3 of 3], 1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Maidenform: Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 3], 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Maidenform: Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 3], 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Maidenform: Miscellaneous [folder 3 of 3], 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Puritan Fashion Corporation: Negotiations, 1973-1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Puritan Fashion Corporation: Master Agreements, Calvin Klein, 1973-1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: Centerfold Industries, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Puritan Fashion Corporation: Calvin Klein-Centerfold [folder 1 of 3], 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Puritan Fashion Corporation: Calvin Klein-Centerfold [folder 2 of 3], 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Puritan Fashion Corporation: Calvin Klein-Centerfold [folder 3 of 3], 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: Chersaw South Carolina, Supplemental Agreements, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement [folder 1 of 3], 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement [folder 2 of 3], 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement [folder 3 of 3], 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Calvin Klein: Master Agreement, Draft Version, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: Thorsby Supplemental Agreements, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: Walterboro South Carolina, Supplemental Agreements, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: Wellford Warehouse Supplemental Agreements, 1983-1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: Supplemental Agreement, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Calvin Klein: New York, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Calvin Klein: Master Agreement, Draft Version [Folder 1 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Calvin Klein: Master Agreement, Draft Version [Folder 2 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Puritan/Calvin Klein: Wellford Correspondence, 1982-1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Puritan/Calvin Klein: Winston Mills Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Calvin Klein: Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 1 of 4], 1979-1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Calvin Klein: Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 2 of 4], 1979-1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)